[{"question": " pheebs? could you get that? please?", "answer": " why? just 'cause you're too lazy to get up off your touchie?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " no! no! it's just that all the people in the entire world that i want to talk to are right here.", "answer": "  okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": "  sucker!", "answer": "  hello?  hey joey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " hey pheebs! listen, uh can you do me a favor? i forgot the pin number to my atm card can, can you get it for me?", "answer": " sure! where is it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " uh, i scratched it on the atm machine down on the corner.", "answer": " ohh! so you're 5639?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": "  ooh, do you want to talk to chandler?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " who was that?", "answer": " uhh, my stunt double. yeah, and y'know, he's getting a little too familiar for my tastes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " well, i'm totally over it chandler. friends forever! don't come out here!", "answer": "  would you mind doing a picture with us?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": "  phoebe?  oh, phoebe, i'm so sorry. have you been here long?", "answer": "  it's okay. what the hell took you so long?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " okay, you can not tell chandler. okay? that i ran into richard.", "answer": " which richard?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " the richard.", "answer": " richard simmons?! oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " noo! my ex-boyfriend richard! y'know the tall guy, moustache?", "answer": " oh! okay, that actually makes more sense. so how was it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " it was, it was really nice. we started talking and i-i ended up having lunch with him.", "answer": " that is so weird! i had a dream that you'd have lunch with richard.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " but again, simmons. go on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " the strange part was, he was really nice, umm and he looks great, but i didn't feel anything at all!", "answer": " ooh! so now why can't we tell chandler?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " because it would totally freak him out and tomorrow's our anniversary. i just don't want anything to spoil that.", "answer": " oh, i can't believe you guys lasted a whole year!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " i know.", "answer": " wow! i owe rachel 20 bucks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " on a totally different bet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " it's almost our anniversary!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " i know. can you believe it? one year ago today i was just your annoying friend chandler.", "answer": " awww! now you're just my annoying friend chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " huh.", "answer": " i got you a present!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " oh, but it's not 'til tomorrow!", "answer": " i know, but you have to open it today!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": "  okay! there you go! it's two tickets to vegas!", "answer": " wow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " for this weekend! oh gosh, it would be perfect, we get to see joey plus we get to start our anniversary celebration on the plane. we can call it out plane-aversary.", "answer": " do we have to?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " okay this is great, but joey said he didn't want any of us out there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " oh, he just doesn't want us to go through any trouble. think of how excited he'll be when we go out and surprise him! plus we get to have our own, ani-vegas-ary! a-nevadaversary!", "answer": " yeah, i think we should see other people.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " but we can go, right?", "answer": " yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " okay!", "answer": " it's a great idea.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " okay, i'm gonna go too!", "answer": " y'know pheebs, it's kinda our  anniversary.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " oh please, you are not gonna ditch again like you did with london.", "answer": " ditch you? phoebe, you were pregnant with the triplets!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " uh-huh, great story! i'm going!", "answer": "  hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " hey, you guys, listen, this weekend we're all gonna go to las vegas to surprise joey! including me!! you wanna go?!", "answer": " well, i guess i could take a couple days off work.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " of course you can take a couple days off work because this trip includes", "answer": " oh no, wait a minute, wait, i've got a presentation tomorrow. i can't miss that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " oh, but i've got tickets to the van gogh exhibit! i've been waiting like a year for this.", "answer": "  art lover!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " what'd you say?", "answer": " i said art lover.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " is that supposed to be an insult?", "answer": " i don't know, i'm very tired.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " so rach, maybe you and i could fly out together saturday.", "answer": " that sounds great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " okay. yeah, that would be nice actually, to have the apartment to myself for a night.", "answer": " oh yeah, so you can walk around naked.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " no! so i can be by myself. y'know? have a little alone time.", "answer": " naked alone time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " no! phoebe just because i'm alone doesn\u0092t mean i wanna walk around naked. i mean, you live alone, you don't walk around naked.", "answer": " uh-huh! why do you think it takes me so long to answer the door?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " so, so far is this trip to vegas better or worse than the trip to london?", "answer": " so it's pretty much the same pheebs.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " yeah, i guess it's a little better now.", "answer": " ah-ha! okay,  las vegas 1, london 0! i'll be right back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": "  happy plane-aversary.", "answer": " aww! i love you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " can i give you a present now?", "answer": " okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " okay!  oh man! don\u0092t tell me i did this!", "answer": " i love the \"i forgot the present\" fake out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " how do you feel about the, \"i really did forgot the present, please forgive me\" not fake out?", "answer": " oh that's okay. don\u0092t worry about it, you can give it to me when we get back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " ohh that's the worse thing that can happen on an anniversary ever!", "answer": "  oh good! all right, so you decided to tell him about the richard thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " what-what richard thing?", "answer": " oh no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " what richard thing?", "answer": "  simmons! go with simmons!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " okay, i umm, i ran into richard yesterday and he asked me if i wanted to go for a bite and i did. the only reason i didn't tell you is because i knew you'd get mad and i didn't want to spoil our anniversary.", "answer": "  i'm not mad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " really?!", "answer": " oh yeah! yeah, so you-you bumped into richard! you grabbed a bite! it's no big deal.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " may i come in?", "answer": " uh, yeah, if you want too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " do you want me too?", "answer": " yeah, sure?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " and um, what-what is that ross?", "answer": " the physical act of love.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  what?! are you crazy?", "answer": " oh so-so you weren't trying to entice me just now with your-your nakedness?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": "  oh god, you saw me?! oh!", "answer": " you weren't trying to entice me with your nakedness.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " noo!! no! you thought, you actually thought i wanted to have sex with you?!", "answer": " no! no!  no!  no-no-no-no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " ohh wow! i\u0092m sorry, but ross you kicked off your shoes!", "answer": " can we, can we just forget this ever happened?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " yes of course, absolutely! you're right. i'm sorry.", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " yes.", "answer": " all right i guess i'm, gonna go pack.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " hey you guys wait! guys!  this place is so much better than london! okay? this lady dressed like cleopatra gave me a coupon, 99 cent steak and lobster dinner. huh!", "answer": " phoebe, you don't eat animals.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " for 99 cents, i'd eat you.  okay, i can totally settle down here. it's got everything i could ever want, including joey! look!  oh! look! hi!", "answer": " oh my god.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " love your condoms my man.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " what-what are you guys doing here? i thought i told you not to come.", "answer": " why are you dressed as a gladiator?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " uhh, because i'm shooting a scene right now. yeah, i uh, i play a gladiator. uh, y'know what? hold-hold on a second.  can we cut? yeah, my-my friends are here, i'm gonna take a little break.", "answer": " who are you talking too?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " they uh director. uhh, her.  all right, all right, it's not a gladiator movie. i work here.", "answer": " why?! what happened?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " well, the movie got shutdown because they ran out of money, so i'm working here 'til it starts up again, if it ever does.", "answer": " i'm so sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " look, i'm sorry i didn't tell ya.  i'm sorry man.", "answer": " no-no, that's okay, apparently there's a new policy where we don't have to share everything with everybody.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " i knew you were not okay with that.", "answer": " so you're a gladiator! wow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " yeah, what-what's going on?", "answer": " monica had lunch with richard.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " dawson?!", "answer": " noo! but that would've been so cool!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " no! her boyfriend richard!", "answer": " it meant nothing! okay? after all this time, how can you not trust me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " when you go lunching with hunky moustache men and don't tell me about", "answer": " you're right. i'm sorry. i should've told you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " aww, there we go.", "answer": " i love vegas!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " i promise you, next time i will absolutely tell you.", "answer": "  next time?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " ooh, so close.", "answer": " there's not gonna be a next time! you can not ever see him again!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " i can not see him? i mean, you can't tell me what to do!", "answer": " that's so funny, because i think i just did!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " oh y'know what? if you're gonna be acting like this all night, i really, i don't even want to be around you.", "answer": " fine with me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " fine! happy anniversary!", "answer": " whoa! whoa! guys! please! come on! come on! this is obviously just a big misunderstanding.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " no it is not!", "answer": " what are you talking\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": "  okay umm, ross? i'm-i'm really warm, so i'm going to be taking off my sweater. now, i'm just letting you know that this is not an invitation to the physical act of love.", "answer": "  yep! that's hilarious!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " i'm sorry. i'm done. i'm done.", "answer": " y'know, last night was embarrassing for you too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " no, not really. i mean you've seen me naked hundreds of times.", "answer": " uh-huh. but it was a first for the rest of my building.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " okay. all right, that's true! but y'know i just don't embarrass that easily.", "answer": " what?! you totally get embarrassed!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " no, i don't! ross, i think i'm just a more secure person than you are.", "answer": " is that so?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " hey, y'know in roman times this was more than just a hat.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " yeah, sure! sure! they would uh, they would scrub the floors with it! they would use it to get the mud off their shoe. and sometimes underneath the horse would get dirty so they would stick it right\u009a", "answer": "  joey, i uh! i can't believe this is how i'm spending my anniversary.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " all right well, i'll take you someplace nice then. look! a guy tipped me a hundred bucks today.", "answer": " whoa!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " yeah-yeah, he was playing blackjack for like an hour and he won $5,000. can you believe that? $5,000!", "answer": " y'know, if i won $5,000 i'd join a gym, y'know build up my upper body and hit richard from behind with a stick!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " wait a minute! why don't i do what that guy did? i'll take this $100 and turn it into $5,000! and then i'll turn that into enough money to get my movie going again!", "answer": " good luck!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " chandler! i don't need luck. i have thought this through!", "answer": " i see.  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": "  thank you.", "answer": " thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " i can't believe this! this is like the worst night ever!", "answer": " y'know monica you had a minor setback in your relationship with chandler. big deal! it's only chandler.  i am so sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " this is crazy! i mean, it's such a stupid argument. i don't even wanna see richard again.", "answer": " so go fix it! go find chandler! he's probably up in your room! tell him that you're sorry and that you love him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " what the? what\u009a", "answer": "  hi! the flight attendant: miss? may i help you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " changing one hundred!  good luck sir.", "answer": "  let's ride.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": "  13.", "answer": " hit me!  ohh man!  wait!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " chandler! you are not gonna believe this! i have found my identical hand twin!", "answer": "  what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " my identical hand twin!", "answer": " what's an identical hand twin?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " what's it sound like? it's a guy with my identical hands! it was incredible! chandler, the dealer's hands were exactly like me! it-it was like looking at my hands in a mirror!", "answer": " are you sure you weren't  looking at your hands in a mirror?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " don\u0092t you see what this means?! i can forget about that stupid movie. i'm gonna be a millionaire!", "answer": "  how?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " look, i don't have it all worked out yet, but it's gotta mean big money! come on! identical hands!", "answer": " again i must go back to, how?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " this is vegas man! people will pay to see freaky stuff! okay, how much would you pay to see this hand  twice? huh?", "answer": "  y'know, i-i can't really put a price on that joe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " hey, are you unsupporting me again?", "answer": " no! no! i support you 100%! i just didn't, i didn't get it right away. y'know now i'm caught up! identical hand twins! it's a million-dollar idea!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " pheebs!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " i found my identical hand twin!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " ohh, you are so lucky!  hey! so, where's monica? did you guys make up?", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " but she just came up here!", "answer": " that was joey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " i wonder where she is. that is so weird.", "answer": " yeah, well, she's probably talking to richard.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " would you stop that! do you wanna know the first thing she said when she came back from her lunch with richard? she didn't feel anything for him. she loves you!", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}, {"question": " yes! now, she feels terrible! she really wants to make up! you gotta find her.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 305, "asentId": 306}, {"question": "  welcome to las vegas.  the flight attendant:  thank you!  enjoy your flight?", "answer": " yes, i did. thank you very much, it was excellent.  the flight attendant:  hope you had a nice flight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 309, "asentId": 310}, {"question": " hello!  ohh, kids love me.", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 317, "asentId": 318}, {"question": " you guys are here! yay!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 321, "asentId": 322}, {"question": " pancho vila?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 325, "asentId": 326}, {"question": " what are you talking about pheebs?  i don't\u009a   oh my god, you drew on me?!", "answer": " hey, you wet my pants!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 327, "asentId": 328}, {"question": " whoa, what kind of party was this?", "answer": " ross, i have been walking around like this since the plane! i can\u0097you have so crossed a line.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 329, "asentId": 330}, {"question": " ugh!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 333, "asentId": 334}, {"question": " that's like the third time that lady's won on a machine i was playing.", "answer": " oooohhh, i'll bet she's one of those people.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 335, "asentId": 336}, {"question": " m-m-mole people?", "answer": " what? no-no, a lurker.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 337, "asentId": 338}, {"question": " oh. what's a lurker?", "answer": " okay when you're playing a machine and it hasn't paid out, a lurker waits for you to give up and then\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 339, "asentId": 340}, {"question": " kills you?", "answer": " no. they swoop in and steal your jackpot.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 341, "asentId": 342}, {"question": " ohhh!", "answer": " uh-hmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 343, "asentId": 344}, {"question": " how do you know about this?", "answer": " my nana used to do it. that's how she paid for all my dance\u0097karate lessons.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 345, "asentId": 346}, {"question": " dance karate?", "answer": " yes, it's a deadly but beautiful sport.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 347, "asentId": 348}, {"question": "  all right, it won't come off!", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 349, "asentId": 350}, {"question": " it won't come off!", "answer": " oh my god! rach-rach, are-are-are you sure?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 351, "asentId": 352}, {"question": " no, actually i took it off then i drew it back on.", "answer": "  hey-hey-hey you made it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 353, "asentId": 354}, {"question": " joey!!", "answer": " all right! hey-hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 355, "asentId": 356}, {"question": " hi!!", "answer": " who's your friend? he's hot!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 357, "asentId": 358}, {"question": "  thanks man.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 359, "asentId": 360}, {"question": " hey listen i uh, talked to chandler, sorry about the movie.", "answer": " no, don't be sorry. i don't need it anymore. i found my identical hand twin!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 361, "asentId": 362}, {"question": " your what?", "answer": " my identical hand twin! the person whose hands are exactly like mine! this thing is a gold mine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 363, "asentId": 364}, {"question": " what?! that's not gonna make you any money!", "answer": " okay. well, if that's how you feel about it, fine! none of you get to live with me in my great big hand-shaped mansion! except uh, you pheebs. you can live in the thumb.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 365, "asentId": 366}, {"question": " all right baby, come on!  yes! yes! i am on fire!", "answer": "  see you later mon.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 367, "asentId": 368}, {"question": " wait chandler, what are you doing?!", "answer": " what does it look like? i'm going home.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 369, "asentId": 370}, {"question": " what? wait! why?  chandler! chandler! wait! i\u0092m sorry, i was just playing for one second! i was trying to find you to tell you that, look if you don't want me to see richard again, i won't! he means nothing to me!", "answer": " come on! i was there!  i know he's the love of your life.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 371, "asentId": 372}, {"question": " not any more.", "answer": " really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 373, "asentId": 374}, {"question": " really!  all right? let's forget about this going home stuff and celebrate our anniversary.  okay, this is empty.", "answer": " yeah, i wanted to make a dramatic scene, but i hate packing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 375, "asentId": 376}, {"question": "  uhh, hey. where's the other guy? the woman dealer: which guy?", "answer": " he's kinda tall, dark hair, hand looks exactly like this.  see? the woman dealer: i don't know about the hands, but the guy that was here before me just went to the bathroom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 377, "asentId": 378}, {"question": " okay!  how you doin'? the woman dealer: very busy.", "answer": " right! okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 379, "asentId": 380}, {"question": "  yes, hello. i have a question. umm, i used your pen to draw on my friend's face.  a beard and a moustache.  thank you.  no, she didn't think so.  i know it's like  anyway, umm well make-up didn't cover it and we've tried everything to get it off and nothing's worked. what-what do we do?  yeah.  uh-huh.  yeah.  oh! okay.  okay, thank you!   yeah, it's not coming off.", "answer": " what?! what else did he say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 381, "asentId": 382}, {"question": " umm, he said he thought i was funny. so\u009a okay, look-look umm, let's just go downstairs, we'll have some fun, and you will forget all about it.", "answer": " ross, no! there is no way i am leaving this room looking like this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 383, "asentId": 384}, {"question": " oh, come on! rach, it's-it's not that bad.", "answer": " ross, i am a human doodle!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 385, "asentId": 386}, {"question": " okay, there was some staring and pointing.", "answer": " okay, i need a, i need a drink!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 389, "asentId": 390}, {"question": " oh, hey y'know, they-they really overcharge you for that stuff.  but who cares?! because it's all on me!   that is, one big drink!", "answer": "  macadamia nut?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 391, "asentId": 392}, {"question": "  umm\u009a wow! that's-that's some pricey nut!", "answer": " hm-mmm!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 393, "asentId": 394}, {"question": " really like those macadamia nuts, huh?", "answer": " nope!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 395, "asentId": 396}, {"question": "  hey pheebs!", "answer": " ohh! you made up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 399, "asentId": 400}, {"question": " yeah, i couldn't be mad at him for too long.", "answer": " yeah, she couldn't live without the chan love.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 401, "asentId": 402}, {"question": " ohh, get a room.", "answer": " we have one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 403, "asentId": 404}, {"question": " oh-oh-oh, yeah!  that's right, you take good care of those babies! joey's hand twin: excuse me?", "answer": " it's me, joey! joey's hand twin: do i know you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 407, "asentId": 408}, {"question": "  joey! joey's hand twin: oh-ho, yeah. yeah, the hand guy.", "answer": " okay, so what are we going to do about this hand twin thing?! joey's hand twin: nothing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 409, "asentId": 410}, {"question": " look, you and i have been given a gift. okay? we have to do something with it. like-like, hand modeling! huh? or-or magic! and you know nasa's gonna wanna talk to us! joey's hand twin:  i have to get back to\u009a", "answer": "  whoa! whoa! whoa! whoa-whoa! we could have our own show! y'know we could clap our hands together people will love it! huh? and-and-and i wrote a song for us!  this hand is your hand! this hand is my hand! oh wait, that's your hand! no wait, it's my hand! joey's hand twin: that's okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 411, "asentId": 412}, {"question": " oh my god, i'm starting to look like my great aunt, muriel.", "answer": "  all right. y'know what? we don\u0092t have to go downstairs! we can bring vegas up to us!  all right, come on, come on, we'll play some blackjack. here we go.  13.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 415, "asentId": 416}, {"question": " hit me!", "answer": "  oohh, 23.  which is what we play to at this casino! you win 10 dollars!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 417, "asentId": 418}, {"question": " i bet 20.", "answer": " you're right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 419, "asentId": 420}, {"question": "  a new pair of shoes for the chan-chan man!  yes!", "answer": " yes! i've-i've never seen a roll like this in my life!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 421, "asentId": 422}, {"question": " that's right baby! okay, what do i want now?", "answer": " okay, ah umm, ah, a 8. ah, a 6?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 423, "asentId": 424}, {"question": " pick a number! that is your only job!", "answer": " 8. 8!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 425, "asentId": 426}, {"question": " thank you!", "answer": " if you get this one, we buy everybody here a steak dinner!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 427, "asentId": 428}, {"question": " yay!!", "answer": " 8!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 429, "asentId": 430}, {"question": " yes!", "answer": " yay!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 431, "asentId": 432}, {"question": "  we're not really gonna buy these people steak dinners are", "answer": " noo!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 433, "asentId": 434}, {"question": " okay, good! okay, what do i want now?", "answer": " ahh, ooh, try a hard 8.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 435, "asentId": 436}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " two fours.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 437, "asentId": 438}, {"question": " 8!: a drunken gambler:  don't you let her go! you're a lucky guy!", "answer": " thank you, mister drunken gambler! okay, you get this and uh, we get the biggest suite in the place!  wait-wait-wait-wait! we  get the biggest suite in the place.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 441, "asentId": 442}, {"question": "  yes!! i love you! i can't even remember what we were fighting about!", "answer": " oh, that's because i had lunch with rich\u0097me neither! okay, what do i want now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 445, "asentId": 446}, {"question": " another hard 8.", "answer": " hard 8?! we should call it easy 8!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 447, "asentId": 448}, {"question": " okay, okay, i tell you what. you roll another hard eight;  and we get married here tonight.", "answer": " go! come on! roll!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 449, "asentId": 450}, {"question": " roll-roll!!", "answer": " shut up!! it just got interesting! commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 451, "asentId": 452}, {"question": " what did you just say?", "answer": " you roll another hard eight and we get married here tonight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 453, "asentId": 454}, {"question": " are you serious?!", "answer": " yes! i love you! i've never loved anybody as much as i love you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 455, "asentId": 456}, {"question": " i've never loved anybody as much as i love you.", "answer": " okay, so if an eight comes up, we take it as a sign and we do it! {whoa! where have i heard that before? matthew perry talking about signs in las vegas. i guess it must've been some movie i saw.} what do you say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 457, "asentId": 458}, {"question": " okay!", "answer": " okay! come on! let's go! all right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 459, "asentId": 460}, {"question": "  okay! that's a four! and where-where's the other one?", "answer": " it went under the table.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 461, "asentId": 462}, {"question": " nobody move!  okay, you look that way; i'll look this way!", "answer": " all right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 463, "asentId": 464}, {"question": " here it is! here it is!", "answer": " that could be a four or a five. it's your call.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 465, "asentId": 466}, {"question": " it's a four.", "answer": " i think so too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 467, "asentId": 468}, {"question": " oh well, lost again.  that's it! you and me, outside!", "answer": " i don't want to see you lose a chunk of that pretty blond hair!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 469, "asentId": 470}, {"question": " be cool!  okay lady, your lurking days are over!", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 471, "asentId": 472}, {"question": " yeah, from now on everyone you lurk, i'm gonna lurk first! you move on to someone else, i'm gonna be one step ahead of you, every single time! and then i'll be on your ass every hour of every day 'til monday, because that's when i go home. when do you leave?", "answer": " also monday.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 473, "asentId": 474}, {"question": "  we need more cards.", "answer": " yeah, and also we need more umm, drinks. hold on a second.  whup, okay.  hello! vegas? yeah, we would like some more alcohol, and y'know what else? we would like some more beers. hello? ohh, i forgot to dial!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 479, "asentId": 480}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " ohh, it's joey! i love joey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 483, "asentId": 484}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 487, "asentId": 488}, {"question": " look-look-look you guys, i need some help! okay? someone is going to have to convince my hand twin to cooperate!", "answer": " i'll do it. hey, whatever you need me to do, i'm your man.   whoa-oh-whoa! are you, are you okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 489, "asentId": 490}, {"question": " yeah! i'm fine! thanks!  hey rach, how you doin'?", "answer": " i'm doin' good, baby. how you doin'?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 491, "asentId": 492}, {"question": " ohh, here's that macadamia nut!", "answer": " ohhh!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 495, "asentId": 496}, {"question": " oops! all right, so what do you want to do now?", "answer": " i wanna get out of the room! y'know, i\u009ai really miss downstairs.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 499, "asentId": 500}, {"question": " well hello! i'm ross!", "answer": " good luck to ya!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 503, "asentId": 504}, {"question": " wow!", "answer": "  hello!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 507, "asentId": 508}, {"question": " i won! i won! i finally won!", "answer": " i won! that was my quarter!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 511, "asentId": 512}, {"question": "  excuse me, sir! this lady played my quarter, this is my money.  the security guard:  is that true miss?", "answer": "  sells drugs to kids. the security guard: what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 515, "asentId": 516}, {"question": " it was my quarter! the security guard:  was it her quarter?", "answer": " how about we talk about this over dinner? the security guard: okay lady, you're out of here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 519, "asentId": 520}, {"question": " no! no, you can't arrest me! no!! i won't go back! i won't go back to that hell hole!! the security guard: i'm just taking you outside!", "answer": " oh, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 521, "asentId": 522}, {"question": " okay, come on, i can't get married until i get something old, something new, something borrowed, and something blue.", "answer": " okay, all right, all right, all right! okay!  okay, here's something, here's something blue and new.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 523, "asentId": 524}, {"question": " you're so efficient. i love you!", "answer": " let's go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 525, "asentId": 526}, {"question": " no-no-no! we need something old!", "answer": " ohh, great, i have condom in my wallet i've had since i was twelve.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 527, "asentId": 528}, {"question": " that'll work!", "answer": " i don't think so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 529, "asentId": 530}, {"question": " okay, now we just need something borrowed!", "answer": "  here just\u009atake this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 531, "asentId": 532}, {"question": " that's stealing!", "answer": " no, we'll-we'll bring it back! just put it under your dress.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 533, "asentId": 534}, {"question": "  ahhh!  joey's hand twin: are you gonna play?", "answer": " no-no, i don't really have any money. not yet, anyway\u009a  joey's hand twin: you can't sit here if you're not gonna play.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 539, "asentId": 540}, {"question": "  hello. my name is regina phalange. i'm a businesswoman in town on business. would you like to see my card?  ooh, what did i do with my file-a-facts? i must've left it in conference room b. joey's hand twin:  14.", "answer": " hit me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 543, "asentId": 544}, {"question": " oh my god! may i just say that you two gentlemen have the exact same hands! they're identical! now, i've never seen anything like that in the business world. joey's hand twin: stop it!", "answer": " uhh, ms. phalange, may i ask you a question as an impartial person at-at this table? joey's hand twin: please stop it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 545, "asentId": 546}, {"question": " wouldn't you pay good money to see these identical hands showcased in some type of a uh, entertainment venue? joey's hand twin:  if you leave now, i will chop off my hand and give it too you!  the security guard:  didn't i just throw you out of here?", "answer": " no, you threw out phoebe. i'm ms. regina phalange. phalange! the security guard: come on, lady!  joey's hand twin: please, please take him too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 547, "asentId": 548}, {"question": " hello! one marriage please!", "answer": " yep, we wanna get married!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 551, "asentId": 552}, {"question": "  dum! dum-dum-dum! dum! dum! dum! dum-dum-dum!", "answer": " what are you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 555, "asentId": 556}, {"question": " oh, that's the wedding march. does, does that freak you out?", "answer": " no, only because that's the graduation song.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 557, "asentId": 558}, {"question": " okay!  this is it!  we're gonna get married!", "answer": " are you sure you wanna do this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s5/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 559, "asentId": 560}]